American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Audiovisual Materials Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid MC001.02.06
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 6, Audio-Visual materials, 1930-1995; 70 boxes; 1 folder; 2 items
  - Photographs, 1930-1979; 9 boxes
    - Portraits, dates not examined; 6 boxes
      - Garbus, Martin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Garrison, Lloyd K., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Gellhorn, Walter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Gunther, John, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Hacker, Louis, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Harris, Patricia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Hays, Arthur Garfield, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2072)
      - Heckscher, August, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Hendel, Samuel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Holmes, John Haynes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Horne, Dr. Frank S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Huebsch, Benjamin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Jacobs, Mrs. Yarnell, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Jones, Dr. John Paul, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Karpatkin, Marvin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Kenyon, Judge Dorothy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Kerney Jr., James, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - McKay, Robert B., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - McNaughton, A.B., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Mazey, Ernest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Malin, Patrick Murphy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2073)
      - Maslow, Will, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Meiklejohn, Alexander, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Meserve, Harry, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Metzenbaum, Howard M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Miller, Byron S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Miller, Reverend Edward, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Miller, Jay, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Millis, Walter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Milner, Lucille, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Moore, William, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Morgan, Charles, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Neier, Aryeh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Nelles, Walter, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Norton, Eleanor Holmes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Parsons, Reverend Edward, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Pemberton, Jr., John de J., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2074)
      - Pilpel, Harriet, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Pinkus, Craig, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Pitkin, Wolcott, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Pratt, Elliot, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Redfield, Emanuel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Reitman, Alan, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Rice, Elmer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Ross, William, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Rubin, Steve (with bombed out car), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Schroeter, Leonard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Schwartzschild, Henry, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Slaff, George, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Speiser, Lawrence, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Stevenson, Adlai, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Stokes, Helen, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Strickland, Ann, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Ten Eyck, Barent, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Tydings, Senator Joseph, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Wechsler, James, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Whiteside, Howard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Williams, Edward Bennett, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Wood, L. Hollingsworth, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
      - Wulf, Mel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2075)
    - Group Photos, 1963; 1 box
      - R. Baldwin, M. Tree, A. Macleish 12/3, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - R. Baldwin, J. Pemberton, P. Malin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - R. Baldwin, A. Schlesinger, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - P. Malin, A. Hays, G.W. Waring, E. Angell, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - J. Pemberton, unidentified, 1963; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - S. Teller, C. Darrow, Brophy, (12/28), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
      - A. Hays (plus negative), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2076)
  - Professional Video Tape, 1970-1979; 9 boxes
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 1; 1 box (Box 2077)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 2; 1 box (Box 2078)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 3; 1 box (Box 2079)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 4; 1 box (Box 2080)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 5; 1 box (Box 2081)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 6; 1 box (Box 2082)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 7; 1 box (Box 2083)
    - The Rights of Americans, 1976; 8; 1 box (Box 2084)
    - Amnesty Spots, 1970s; 1 box (Box 2085)
  - Microfiche, 1980; 1 box
    - Microfiche, index cards, and program guide for Microsources "The Bill of Rights in the 20th Century," an instructional collection of primary source material, 1980; 1 box (Box 2085A)
  - Oversized Materials, 1931-1992; 18 boxes; 1 folder
    - ACLU Printed Materials, 1931-1992; 11 boxes
      - Civil Liberties, 1931-1992; 3 boxes (Box 2086, Box 2087, Box 2088)
      - Affiliate Publications, undated; 6 boxes (Box 2089, Box 2090, Box 2091)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 2 boxes (Box 2095, Box 2096)
    - Subject Files, dates not examined; 3 boxes
      Printed Material culled from Series 2, Project Files and Series 3, Subject Files includes:
      - Civil Rights, Government, International Civil Liberties, Labor and Business, Mass Communications, and Mental Health Issues, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2097)
      - Military Rights (Amnesty Project) and Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2098)
      - Native Americans and Women's Rights, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 2099)
    - Outside Organizations, dates not examined; 4 boxes
      - AFL-CIO News - Clarion, undated; 1 box (Box 2100)
      - Civil Rights News - Just Us, undated; 1 box (Box 2101)
      - Lancaster Independent - Quash, undated; 1 box (Box 2102)
      - Rights - Miscellaneous pamphlets and posters, undated; 1 box (Box 2103)
    - Posters, 1969; undated; 1 folder (Folder Oversize folder 1)
      Includes: 1) Lesbian and Gay Rights Project poster; 2) "Owners of the War Machine are the Real Criminals" (Chicago); 3) 1969 reprint from The Advance: "Dissent: The Basic Right of a Free People."